You pull her.
I never expected it before.
That aerial yoga would have so many
physical interactions.
What should this be called?
Is it very sweet?
The focus isn't even on doing yoga.
Getting more and more relaxed.
Very good.
One, two, three, four.
The two of them are a good match.
What I want to say to her is
She really has reached my heart.
I want to express it with this song.
Actually, Yonghao is
different from others to me.
He gives me special care.
You asked me
whether I really have
feelings of liking.
About this, I think
I definitely do like him.
I want to continue this relationship.
And work on this relationship together with you.
Love is so wonderful.
Yes.
Go on Soul APP now.
Interesting souls, free encounters.
This program is brought to you by the app popular among young people,
exclusively sponsored by Soul APP.
Global beauty and health products
Visit the Watsons mini program
Thank you for the beauty of health and the health of beauty
Jointly sponsored and broadcast by Watsons
Welcome, everyone, to
Tencent Video's original
mature dating observation reality show
"Half-Grown Lovers" Season 4
I'm Xie Nan
Let's welcome our observation room guests
Ms. Du Sujuan
Xu Yiyang
Zhang Chunye
Tang Yixin
Lu Hu
And our Xia Zhiguang
Welcome, everyone
The upcoming two-day, one-night trip
is actually the final stage.
Whether they want to pursue someone,
show their charm,
maintain a relationship,
or want to
redefine the relationship,
this might be their only chance
to spend time together.
It's considered the last opportunity.
It's the final chance.
Honestly,
everyone has their own issues to resolve.
In the last episode, we saw
Luo Junfan and Xia Xia.
Right.
It seems Luo Junfan also
has softened his attitude a bit.
He wants to reinterpret
whether that fondness is really related to liking someone.
Are they connected?
Yes.
And so far, Luo Junfan
has only gone on one date.
Everyone,
Yes.
I also want to see how he has changed.
Including the pair of Wo Wo and the others.
Yes.
Yes, that's right.
Everything felt really good before.
Yes.
But honestly,
as the time to enter real life approaches,
it's getting closer.
Will their relationship change?
Of course.
There's also another important highlight and suspense.
It's whether Xia Zhiguang can put on the lock or not.
Let me tell you,
the rules are different today.
Chunye, please guide us.
Okay.
To help Teacher Xia lock in as soon as possible,
so right from the start,
we'll go straight into our usual
Soul Heart-to-Heart Moment.
We saw everyone in the cabin
has already started a new round of invitations.
So for this episode,
our initial Heart-to-Heart Moment
will have us guessing something different.
In a moment,
we'll see four sentences.
And these four sentences
each correspond to one of four pairs.
We need to figure out which sentence
matches which pair.
Among them are "Qing Renjie Pair,"
"Ting Tian Pair,"
"Wan You Ying Li,"
and "Xia Luo Te Fan Nao Pair."
We just have to match them.
Global beauty and health products.
Search for the Watsons mini program on WeChat.
Get it in as fast as thirty minutes.
Please watch Watsons' Heartfelt Reasoning Moment.
When I saw this sentence,
I got goosebumps.
Which one?
I simply can't
choose whether I like you or not.
Come on, friends.
Don't overthink it.
We're really just guessing without watching the video.
It's just a kind of intuition.
Mr. Du, what will you choose?
Let's look at the negative answers first.
Let's eliminate some options, right?
Let me take a look.
It kind of makes sense.
There's some logic to it, right?
Mr. Du is done for.
We're exactly the same.
Then are we both going down together again?
I think we make sense.
Yeah, I'm confident.
I'm confident too.
Yeah.
Nan, we're the same.
That spring is Hou Chengjie.
Didn't Kaka already get to know Mr. Su before?
That's why it's called "the mantis stalks the cicada."
And the oriole is behind, and behind, and still behind.
Wan Xiao said that about me.
I'm the one behind, behind, getting ready to catch you.
That's what it means.
Is my spring coming?
Don't.
Maybe I'm your autumn.
We're the same.
Yeah, I'm just like Xin.
You two are the same.
We're the same.
Hu Ge
You have your own unique style.
Standing out on your own.
Right?
Huzi stands out alone.
So if I put on a lock today,
this is for real.
Then you need to put on ten.
As someone who's followed our show
for four seasons,
I've noticed that our show
every time I try to guess based on their relationship logic
and my understanding of them
and their relationships,
I'm always wrong.
My analysis is off.
So this time, I'm trying a different approach.
Open the Soul app
and meet interesting souls who understand you.
Next, we move on to
the Soul True Feelings Reveal moment.
Suzhou
This sunny couple
You really are something.
The sunshine is really nice today.
Yeah.
Let's ride a paddle boat.
Okay.
That old man looks really handsome.
You might be handsome when you get old too.
A very handsome little old man.
Wowo, go in from this side.
There are two of us.
We're together.
Let's go.
So comfortable.
To have sunshine like this in January,
and this kind of temperature,
it's just perfect.
Yeah.
It really has that kind of
Jiangnan charm in it.
I really enjoy walking along these little alleys by the water.
Actually, just strolling down this little street
is quite nice too.
I think it's great to arrive at an ancient town.
I like places that feel lively and full of everyday life.
It just gives me a real sense of life.
Because usually, when I'm alone,
I rarely get that feeling of real life.
Let me take a photo.
You take pictures of the scenery, and I take pictures of you.
Look at the ones I took.
How's my composition?
You made me look like a...
So good-looking.
I think your side profile is unbeatable.
You really...
Are you serious?
Then I think it looks good.
You're photographing the scenery.
I'm photographing you taking pictures.
I really enjoy taking landscape photos.
There are beautiful views in her eyes.
And in my eyes, there is her.
Look.
Does Brother Hou take lyric-writing jobs?
Get in touch, seriously.
Really.
Okay.
Let me see how your photos turned out.
Let me see.
There are actually a lot of people in here.
Your camera is full of variety.
What's going on?
What do you mean?
What?
This was when I looked up that day.
I suddenly saw the two of them.
Standing here in coats, they looked great.
Where is this?
This is the media room.
Looks really nice.
Then I was sitting on the floor.
I saw the two of them.
I started to get jealous.
Look.
In my photo album,
all the photos are for you.
They're all for you.
They're all of you.
So all of this is mine, right?
So mine is too much, then.
You seem a bit unhappy.
Your expression just now
seemed a little off.
Is that right?
But you're here, aren't you?
No, this—
No way.
How could there not be?
We'll walk around here for a bit later.
Why does it feel a bit shaky?
You really have a cold constitution.
Have some hot soup later.
Okay.
I want to buy you a little souvenir.
Take a look.
Is there anything you want?
Great, I'm happy.
This is a fridge magnet.
Buy a few more things.
Actually, you don't have to buy just one.
Alright.
See if there's anything you want.
When we get to that street, I want to say something.
It's best if it's something he wants and likes.
Then I'll give him a souvenir.
I want to eat.
Pick a skewer of strawberries.
And get one with grapes too.
Let the kid have one.
It's okay.
You eat first.
Let's go.
It's pretty tasty.
This strawberry is so sweet.
So sweet.
I suddenly figured out what I want.
Can you draw this quickly?
Yes.
A colored one takes about ten minutes.
You want this one.
I want this one.
Alright.
Let's go with this one then.
You two are sitting here, right? Okay.
You have to make girls look pretty when you draw them.
Whether it looks like me or not doesn't matter.
Just make me look good.
I want the same.
It doesn't matter if it looks like me.
Just make it look nice.
So it doesn't matter if we sit here or not.
Right?
Just make it look good.
Really?
We still have to sit.
Or you two can go for a walk and come back to pick it up.
Yeah, take a photo and leave it here.
When you come back, I can check it.
Let me take a look.
Check.
Her most distinctive feature is
a small face.
Your face is smaller than mine.
Then make her face a bit bigger.
So cute.
Really cute.
Am I really this chubby?
Yeah, I think so too.
Can you make her face a bit smaller?
Sure.
You can only make it smaller, not bigger.
Yes, that's fine.
Because her face is much smaller than mine.
Draw the girl's face smaller.
Is my face really this round?
No, it's not.
I'm honestly a bit shocked.
Girls look like this because they have collagen.
You only get this look if you have collagen.
Now I just...
calmly enjoy your compliments.
But it doesn't really look like me, anyway.
Yeah.
How about this?
I want to draw another one.
We actually wanted two anyway.
One for each of us.
Thank you.
I can just draw based on this one.
And for hers,
I think it could be a bit slimmer and longer.
Just like that.
Once it's drawn like this,
What surprised me during the drawing process
was how incredibly attentive he is.
Not just to me,
but to others as well.
He put a lot of thought into that painting.
Can you cover this part with her hair?
Just draw a strand of hair over it.
That's okay, right?
I think this is just right.
Just a little bit more.
That's it.
This drawing is pretty good.
It even makes the two of us look a bit
like a married couple.
This couple is just so sweet.
Looks great, really great.
This one is really good.
Very nice.
Absolutely amazing.
With Teacher Hou’s strict supervision,
we finally have a perfect piece of art.
All done.
Okay.
Thank you.
Satisfied.
Happy.
Yours looks a bit too amateur.
Gained a lot.
It really has to be you, Teacher Hou.
What’s up?
It’s just so creative.
Today I feel that the two of us
have naturally entered into
a really good relationship.
Starting from the paddle boat,
to the moment we shared
a single candied hawthorn stick,
it made me feel
like we were really dating.
The care and attention he gives me
and the feelings he shows me
are already perfect in my eyes.
A guy as wonderful as him
probably makes every girl’s heart flutter.
Qing Renjie
Then let's tidy up a bit.
Okay.
Slow down.
Be careful not to slip.
What should we do?
Is this figure for real?
This activity is pretty intimate.
Careful.
If the water is a bit hot,
just get in slowly, okay?
It's at the bottom, right?
Yeah.
Be a little more careful.
It might be a bit hot.
It's a little hot.
Wait a second.
I was just thinking
Didn't you want to try some water sports?
Sure
Like maybe go diving or something
I could learn to swim first
Dog paddle
This really shouldn't be soaked for too long.
That's how it is.
Exactly.
Are you happy right now?
I, right now...
Right now...
Do you feel now...
Are you happy being here with me right now?
Do you feel happy in this situation?
It's pretty good.
I'm very happy.
Do you feel uncomfortable in any way?
No.
That's good.
Then I'll rest for another two minutes.
Oh no, I wrapped you up like a zongzi.
Let's go.
Hey, have you played this kind of game before?
I mean, with someone other than your coach?
No, I haven't.
I've only played with my coach.
Have you learned how to play?
I've only taken one or two lessons.
I've pretty much forgotten everything.
Let me teach you the basic moves first.
The drop shot and the forehand swing.
Okay.
As for playing tennis,
it was the day we went to do aerial yoga.
She started talking about it with Lao Luo.
Actually, both of them
are quite interested in tennis.
And as for me,
I had tried tennis a little before.
Just took one or two lessons.
Although among all the sports I do,
this isn't something I'm good at.
I swing from this side, right?
But I still want to try, because of her.
I want to work hard to learn.
So I can share
her enjoyment.
I think that's a really great thing.
Actually, the two of them are pretty good together.
We
won't worry about the rules.
Let's just play however we want.
Just hit the ball over, that's it.
Okay.
Wait a moment.
Bro
I have to dive to catch this ball.
Let me try again.
A bit softer.
Nice shot.
Perfectly missed.
Right now I feel like
two noobs pecking at each other.
Mainly because I suck.
It's fine, nice shot.
Noob Number One
Noob Number Two
I'm the big noob
Feels like an elementary schooler
Got it
Nice shot
Alright, Noob Number Two narrowly lost
A close loss
Noob Number Two, keep it up
Noob Number Two
Noob Number One
Run for it
Nice shot
That was a great shot
One more, Noob Number Two
Noob Number Two is gradually finding
the feel for serving
Nice shot
I really like the vibe of their conversation
You say something, I respond
Just a bit short
I think there's already that
momentum to start playing
In this round
Isn't it getting more interesting now?
See, this is just—
They've started fighting.
Yeah.
Now it's back and forth.
Absolutely not
If we can hit
ten more balls,
let's finish and go eat.
Because I'm hungry.
Okay, sure.
We have to hit ten balls quickly.
Alright.
Eat.
Beef slices.
Duck intestines.
Frozen tofu.
Enoki mushrooms.
Goose intestines.
That's great!
They can match each other's rhythm, right?
Yeah.
It's me again.
Your penalty is to eat one later.
Spicy cilantro.
If you lose, you have to eat a cilantro.
No problem.
Today I really let go of my nerves.
Let down my guard.
Let go of some of my burdens.
I can be more relaxed when facing him.
For a moment, I thought
maybe this kind of state is actually
the most comfortable state.
Nice shot!
I even tried to scoop it up with my hands.
I used both hands.
And then,
Wanwan is actually quite an interesting person.
Sometimes,
the way he smashes the ball with so much force
makes me feel that he's a bit
silly.
But it's actually pretty cute.
Alright, you eat.
Today is
the day for Rookie No.1 and Rookie No.2's
mutual pecking.
Because honestly, towards Wanwan,
I've never had any filters.
Maybe it started from zero,
and gradually developed some fondness.
Just these little piggy feet,
I wouldn't trade them for anything.
So actually, during the date back then,
it was very relaxed.
Sweating wasn't because of spiciness.
(It was from practicing tennis) Practiced until I cried.
I was pretty much just being myself.
Wan Xiao handled it pretty well.
Yeah.
Some of the reactions she gave
were things he also enjoyed.
Right.
Let’s walk off the meal.
Walk off the meal.
Take a walk, help with digestion.
This is my ideal kind of life.
So far, today there’s nothing
that’s really bothering or confusing me.
Right now, I feel very relaxed.
And I had some delicious food.
And played tennis.
And now I’m strolling through the city.
Sounds like a perfect day.
Yeah, today is just perfect.
Nice.
City walks are so comfortable.
This is how dating should be.
So after you came to the house,
did you notice anything?
What I noticed were those things
that I saw during the New Year’s Eve party.
Liang Tian and Yunting.
And during the first date,
I noticed you and Lao Su.
What?
So you really are...
Yeah.
I know.
You're really brave.
Right?
I really think you're brave now.
If it were me,
I would just back off.
Yeah, based on how I used to be,
that's exactly what I would have done.
But later I started to think,
my thoughts were like what you said yesterday
when we talked in the car.
How you see Liang Tian and Lao Su,
it's kind of similar to this.
I thought if you two hadn't made things official,
at least I could express my feelings.
That would be okay.
I understand.
I wouldn't force anything either.
I'm just saying,
our story is actually pretty similar.
Yeah, a bit.
It's like the mantis stalks the cicada, but the oriole is behind, and then there's someone else behind that.
It's all so complicated.
Impressive.
He used a scenario as a metaphor, and it was really clever.
When he was observing me,
it was just like when I was observing
Liang Tian and Su Yonghao in that situation.
So I understood it instantly.
Why he could understand me.
Because he was doing the same thing.
Looking back now,
he might have started
observing me since New Year's.
I'll just pick the one next to me.
Princess carry.
Help!
This feeling is that you can always look back.
Yes, as long as you look back, I'll always be here.
I love you.
It simply means I love you.
The teacher even brought rice cakes.
Yes.
That's awesome.
I added everything you mentioned.
But unfortunately, I couldn't find green bamboo shoots.
They just don't sell them over there.
So I just had to make do.
I truly felt
that this guy really is
constantly putting in effort, little by little.
He doesn't even mention it.
He just does it quietly.
He gives me a sense of security.
So honestly,
from last night's invitation
to today's date,
my feelings for him have grown a lot.
And I want to take the initiative to get to know him better.
I'm really into him now.
That's pretty perfect too.
Yeah.
So is your dad tall
or is your mom tall?
Neither of my parents is tall.
My dad is 1.74 meters.
My mom is 1.67 meters.
And then
Me? Yeah,
I'm over 1.9 meters.
It's just that as a kid, I could eat and sleep a lot.
My mom said I grew outwards first,
then shot up in height.
Actually, my younger brother is quite tall too.
But he never grew taller than me.
Because he was too picky with food when he was little.
So in the end, he grew to 1.88 meters.
So that means,
maybe if I eat more,
I could reach 1.72 or 1.73 meters.
Yeah.
Eat more green onions and cilantro.
Then you'll shoot up in height.
At first, I was pretty worried
that our date this time would be awkward.
But actually,
the final outcome really gave me
a lot of reassurance.
Going on a date with her gives me
a very comfortable and secure feeling.
In front of her,
I can be myself without worry.
I can open up.
It's the kind of comfort I really like.
It's the kind of atmosphere an introvert really loves.
And because of her presence,
I realized
that I can have this kind of courage too.
What should we eat later?
How about we buy some candied chestnuts?
Sure.
I don't think I'm very good at peeling chestnuts.
I always end up breaking them into pieces.
If they're broken, I just bite them with my teeth.
This conversation
I like this kind of homely,
everyday little chats.
If they're broken, I just bite them with my teeth.
Mr. Luo, Mr. Luo, what is this?
He asked Xia Xia out.
Hello
What are you doing tomorrow?
Nothing.
Then let's go out tomorrow.
Then shall we go out and have fun tomorrow?
Is that okay?
Okay.
Go out and play alone.
Is that okay?
See you downstairs when you wake up.
Okay.
Alright.
See you tomorrow then.
See you tomorrow.
Why do you seem a bit confused, Xia Xia?
She is confused.
Totally unexpected.
But she was still quite
happy
Yeah
looking forward to it
She even snuck out to take a look
After receiving the message yesterday
I thought about it all night
The most important thing for me
is to have another conversation with Xia Xia
I also hope
to have a deep conversation
After I turned that down
our relationship actually started to regress
And after it regressed
because I felt guilty towards her
I actually started to pay more attention to her
and realized that she is still an outstanding person
I'm appreciating her from a different perspective.
She is someone
who, for example, is very dedicated.
She does things for others.
Xia Xia is cooking here by herself.
The three of us are playing with fire here.
I notice that she
has even more wonderful qualities.
For example, painting.
Add a little more here.
Add a bit of white here.
Nanjing University of the Arts
Its graduation exhibition is on May 20th.
You'll notice that whether it's Guo Guo,
Ka Ka,
or even Liang Tian,
they all go to her to talk about their feelings.
She really cares about others' emotions.
So she is
a very charismatic person.
She's a very free-spirited girl.
Really.
She just jumped right down.
She's so cool.
So my impression has changed.
Actually, there have been a lot of changes.
Living in a tent outdoors.
At one point, Xia Xia and I had a conversation.
I said, "Can you unzip the tent a bit?"
Let's look at each other through the curtain.
Friend on the other side.
Who are you calling?
I'm calling you.
What's up?
Open the curtain.
Can't see
Can't see it
I can see an outline
Actually, at that moment I felt
the two of us were a bit like we had gone back to our childhood
having a conversation like little kids
In this moment, I feel
we weren't like before
with that awkward feeling
So for me, this feeling
is really, really good
You can do it!
During the tug-of-war,
Xia Xia would always cheer us on with all her might.
Slow down.
Be careful.
All that concern piled up like a mountain.
Be careful, don't get hurt.
It's no problem for me to change my pile of socks.
We didn't win back the hat in the game.
Today, we'll win it all back.
Actually, I've always wanted to talk to Xia Xia alone.
Just the two of us, to have a conversation.
Because at that time, I felt
some things hadn't been explained clearly.
It's like if you haven't cleaned your house properly,
it's hard to invite guests over.
Actually, I still have another date.
It's one that I was late for.
I didn't make it in time.
Actually, if we keep spending time together,
and you don't jump to conclusions, you'll find
that your feelings for this person
will keep getting stronger.
So I have a new feeling about this now.
Often, we overthink things.
It's better to just take more action.
I think it's necessary to take the first step.
Just like when I walked into the cabin.
I'm still missing one date.
I want to make up for the date I was late for.
And I need to put an end to some of my past mistakes.
Draw a line under them.
And start to change.
Suddenly, my image became much greater.
Luo Junfan's character arc
Why is it so complete?
And then there's such clear self-reflection later on.
And it leads to real action.
He suddenly became admirable.
Alright.
I'll add him back on WeChat.
Just kidding.
We've watched several couples go on dates.
Yangyang, what do you think of Xiao Hou's date this time?
How was the arrangement?
I think our Teacher Hou
is really impressive.
Even a hot spring date like this,
he could come up with it.
So I think
it's quite mature, efficient, and romantic.
And this time,
they went on a trip to Suzhou.
They actually traveled light.
But I think it's fine,
because they had the Watsons Black Label travel set.
With one set in hand,
you have everything you need.
It includes things like face masks and body lotion,
as well as face towels and cleansing wipes.
It's perfect for spontaneous trips.
And if you order through the Watsons WeChat mini program,
it can be delivered to your hotel front desk in as fast as thirty minutes.
I think it's really convenient.
I think Teacher Hou's thoughtful planning
is something Watsons can provide for everyone too.
But sometimes these details
can really determine the success or failure of a date.
Yes.
Right.
And just now, when Yangyang mentioned details,
I also noticed a detail.
It was when they got in the car.
Hou Chengjie said,
You know,
the place in Suzhou I'm taking you to
is actually the same distance as going to your workplace on Monday
—about an hour and a half drive.
The time it takes from our cabin
is the same.
Right.
The task on Monday morning is
to take you to work.
It's about an hour and a half drive.
When you go to work,
the distance from here to your workplace
is about the same.
I really like this sentence.
Because it's obvious that Wo Wo is
someone who values her job a lot.
In a way, he
is easing your concerns.
You won't have to spend extra time
on the commute.
Right.
Yes, very respectful.
It's perfect.
Let's take a look at the pair, Xiaoxiao and Kaka.
I have a feeling.
No matter if it was with me, Brother Zhang, or Zhang Chenxi before,
or with Yonghao,
Kaka has always taken on a certain role.
It's me who creates the atmosphere on the spot,
or eases the awkwardness,
and brings up topics.
But in her dates with Wanwan,
everything just seems to happen naturally.
And it feels even more like
Wanwan is the one guiding her.
Yes, they are a good match.
They're just right for each other, Teacher Du.
When the right people are together,
neither side needs to try too hard.
That's right.
Now, when you see the two of them together,
they both feel very relaxed.
That's how it should be.
So, as the saying goes,
when you give someone else a chance,
you're also giving yourself a chance.
Yes.
I think when she slowed down before,
she was also reflecting on herself,
and figuring out what she truly likes.
Yes.
It's because only Wanwan
could understand someone with a personality like Kaka.
Right.
He actually saw the vulnerable side of me.
So I think that was a turning point.
Yes.
Another touching thing is
that from Wanwan's perspective, he always mistakenly thought
that Kaka had many stories and connections with others.
But he still chose
to act as if nothing happened.
He cooked when it was time to cook,
and treated you well when he should.
And I think the best kind of guidance
is through actions.
Like we saw with the previous couple,
the reason we all felt comfortable watching them
is that both couples could handle each other's emotions well.
Right.
Isn't that so?
Yes.
And I think good guidance
is mutual.
I think it has to be both people
no matter if
I inspired you in one way,
and you encouraged me in another.
You do it together.
If it's always just one person
guiding the other,
I think over time, things will become unbalanced.
Right.
Yeah, look at Wo Wo and Xiao Hou.
The two of them guide each other.
His sensitivity guides her.
Her rationality guides him.
So he's very balanced.
You need to express yourself in various ways.
Body language.
Eye contact.
Yes.
Including these small interactions.
These are actually ways to keep love fresh.
They are very important keys.
Yes, very important.
Are you cold?
Yes, I am.
Why don't we find somewhere warmer?
The wind is too strong.
Let's go inside first.
Do you like playing in the snow?
Yes, I do.
I used to play in the snow a lot when I was little.
But it was at my grandma's house.
Hello.
Are you renting some clothes?
Yes.
Size 175.
Thank you.
Size 190.
Okay, thank you.
Alright, that's good.
So now we can...
...change in this fitting room.
Should I turn around like this? Walk in a circle?
Like this.
Do you need help tying it?
It's okay.
Let me help you tie it.
It's so hot, help!
Tell me if it's too tight.
You're so thoughtful.
Really.
I remember when I was little,
my parents would help me tie it.
Then, when I ran to the snowfield,
the first thing I did was
jump into that pile of snow.
Tying it like this is fine.
All done.
Okay.
Alright, ready.
Let's go.
You can see your breath now.
There's snow now.
Stepping on the snow.
So beautiful.
It's all white.
It's so dreamy.
I could come here to have fun.
Yeah, this place is really nice.
Let's play in the snow.
What should we do now?
It has five floors.
Okay.
And each floor has different facilities.
Alright.
I think we're over here now.
There should be these activities to try.
They said this one is the most fun.
Is it a slide?
It seems to be something like an aerial drop.
Let's go to the top first.
There are so many things here.
Good choice finding this place.
Snow mountain jump platform.
This is interesting.
This is so thrilling.
Are you afraid of heights? You're not, right?
I am afraid of heights.
But I really like this kind of thing.
That's what makes it exciting.
You're asking for trouble.
Not good at it, but still love to play.
This is so scary.
It's terrifying.
It's kind of interesting.
Don't look down.
I won't.
Stand on the white platform.
Yes, half squat.
Squat down a little.
That's right.
Teacher, I'm a little scared.
This is so scary.
It's okay, you can do it.
I can do it.
Yes.
I just need to fall back, right?
Is this like bungee jumping?
Bungee jumping.
Just fall back.
Okay.
Three, two, one.
So interesting.
Does it feel fun?
It's fun, but only for a moment.
I want to see how he gets down.
Don't look.
Here, grab this with both hands.
Don't grab the red one, okay?
It's really pretty scary.
It's fine, just don't look back.
Will you push me?
I won't push you.
Can you push me?
Still not coming down.
So slow.
Be a little braver.
I can't be any braver.
How long did it take you to mentally prepare for this?
Fall back, that's right.
Okay.
Don't be too funny.
This is so bittersweet.
Let's go, teacher.
Sometimes Xiao Hu can only
push himself forward.
But it's really hard for someone afraid of heights to overcome it.
Sure.
Okay.
Thank you.
How was it?
I thought it would drop more before it started going up.
I thought so too.
So my legs were shaking the whole time up there.
And I just couldn't bring myself to jump.
I could tell.
I was filming here.
I was wondering why you still weren't jumping.
How long do you need to psych yourself up?
Why are you so timid?
Too timid, teacher.
Because it's a backward jump.
So I asked the teacher,
"Can you push me?"
Let me do it.
Okay.
I was going to kick you down with one foot.
I was thinking about what kind of pose to use later
to push you down.
Actually, I think kicking you down isn't interesting.
It should be you standing there,
and when you're about to fall,
just a little push with one finger,
and then, oh, you fall down.
I think that's a bit cooler.
Kicking with your foot doesn't feel elegant at all.
I want to be a graceful lady.
So what line will you use?
What line?
Let me think.
This one.
Just this.
Okay, then I'll just keep screaming all the way.
Just like that.
Go ahead.
This angle.
Okay.
Slightly bend your knees.
Can you lean back?
Yes, I can.
Don't stare, and don't jump this step.
Okay.
Come to the center.
A bit slower.
Step back a little more.
A little more.
Okay, this is good.
That's fine.
You can start when you're ready.
Ready.
Okay, lower your head.
Don't look anymore.
It's okay.
Three, two, one, that's it.
That's it.
This time, I invited Liang Tian out to have fun.
I hope she's looking forward to it too.
Let's really let off some steam.
And make some happy memories.
This feels great.
Because a few days ago, I made her...
Maybe there were some misunderstandings or hurt feelings.
Let's move on to the next activity.
We're back to the fridge again.
Now it's the orange's perspective.
If it's frozen, it should be the dumpling's perspective.
This part is really cute too.
Hello.
I'm a kimchi dumpling.
Who are you?
I'm strawberry ice cream.
Strawberry ice cream.
Why are you so sweet?
That's what they said.
You're right.
No one is right.
I'm strawberry ice cream.
Strawberry ice cream.
Why are you so sweet?
Me.
Why am I a kimchi dumpling?
You chose it yourself.
Who can you blame?
That's so mean.
You don't care about the dumpling at all, do you?
You only care about being ice cream.
Chive-flavored dumpling.
Those two can actually play together.
That's just too much.
Come on, let's go play with that tire.
This place is actually pretty fun.
This is really fun.
How do you use this thing?
Let me pull it for you.
Thanks.
You need to pull the small one here too.
This looks like a ski glove.
Alright, let's go.
Is it here?
Come, sit. You two are together, right?
Yes.
Are you ready?
Okay.
Teacher.
Scared me to death.
Those two really are a good match.
Yeah.
It does seem like they're actually getting sweet together.
I think Liang Tian looks quite happy.
It must have been an arrangement she didn't expect.
Thinking back to the happiness of being a child,
it's so simple.
Goodbye.
These are things I might never
forget for the rest of my life.
They've become sweet memories.
I'm going to slide down the slide.
This is so much fun. It's really amazing.
Here we go.
That's kind of funny.
This is so much fun.
It's spraying snow.
There's even snow, really.
You can't pack this snow together.
It's not real snow.
It's artificial snow.
I knew you would pull this trick.
I wouldn't be so rude.
I'll help you look for who did it.
It wasn't me.
Can you help me find out who it was?
It was that kid.
What are you doing?
We only have one bullet.
That was a perfect throw.
Wishing you lots of good luck in the new year.
My leg is injured.
I'm not playing anymore.
Do you want to let go with your right hand?
I've hidden everything.
That was really fun.
Why is there another one on the left?
Smoke grenade.
(We're about to) catch up with that kid from earlier.
Let's catch up to him. Go.
We're about to catch up.
(Kid,) run!
This date has a great atmosphere.
It's snowing.
Do you want to try it?
It feels like Sister Tian is the kind of person
who would be tricked away by an older boy.
I think we should get straight to the point.
Okay.
It's about Xiao Hu's date this time.
The conversation in his room.
Did he solve the problem?
Did he play a role?
He did play a role.
Yes.
But whether it was solved, that's hard to say.
But it made a big difference for Liang Tian.
We can go over it.
A few things he said.
First, he said
that maybe what I expressed before
wasn't very accurate.
Now what I want to tell you is
I want to continue.
Yes, and he also said
I want to work on this relationship with you.
I think this sentence is very important.
He said it really well.
As soon as he said that,
I immediately thought better of him.
Because I think
this shows a lot of growth.
I was confused before
about what Liang Tian actually likes about him.
But after watching everything,
I feel that Liang Tian likes his simplicity.
Yes.
Xiao Hu is actually
a very simple person too.
Maybe because he can't figure out
a lot of things,
he ends up being very simple.
So being together is easy and happy.
You can feel it.
When Liang Tian is with him,
she shows a childlike
innocent smile.
Yes.
Now Tian-jie is a bit...
I don't want to torture myself either.
It's just that I feel
I feel the same way.
Yeah.
I feel the same too.
If he can give an answer,
then I'll just enjoy the present for now.
Right.
Let's talk about the outcome later.
Just now, when we were playing in the snow,
I also had a feeling
of really living in the moment.
Yeah.
I don't know why.
No, it's just that I'm not looking for that answer anymore.
I understand.
Because that answer
is still too far away for our relationship.
Right?
Yes.
You still need to give him time to grow.
Now we feel
what we appreciate more
is that his affection for Liang Tian has overcome
his fear of that kind of relationship he's not good at
that fear
Yes
What we admire about him is
he dares to say, "I like you so much"
It's different from his past relationships
Because I like her
I'm trying to face this fear
But there's still a problem that hasn't been solved
which is what everyone is worried about
Can I really overcome this fear?
It's still a problem
Right, will this condition relapse?
Yes.
Is it possible that he went back again?
For some reason.
Yes, for now we can only say
take it one step at a time.
At least this time, he followed his heart.
Actually, I think Liang Tian
also knows in her heart
that this problem isn't solved.
But I'm willing to give him a chance.
Why?
Because Liang Tian really likes Xiao Hu too.
Look at the two of them.
There's such a big age difference.
But when they're together having fun,
they're like children.
I think this might be
the charm that Liang Tian can't resist.
But this relationship
still needs to be observed.
It depends on how Xiao Hu manages it going forward.
This relationship.
You can't just rely on Liang Tian alone.
Come on.
Let's keep watching.
The pair I'm most curious about is coming up.
Teacher Luo
How did those two end up together? I'm a bit...
Yeah.
To put it simply, it means they have no feelings for me.
Don't fall into the trap.
Don't dig a pit for me here.
Wenzhou, Zhejiang
Seems like it.
Press one.
Then that bag was given to me.
So I accepted it.
Thank you.
It's going home with big brother, right?
Yeah.
Look at the sun.
The sunset.
It's especially orange.
This is so moving.
I was at Yichi Garden
and had a meal with someone else.
Who?
Not like some people
who can still hold hands when they're on a date with someone else.
Here they come.
Quick, take your hand out.
Is there anything about that hot spring besides feeling restrained?
Those muscle lines.
A physical sense of attraction.
That smile seems to say it all.
The visual impact is really strong.
What girl wouldn't be moved?
Ms. Kaka is something else.
Let me hide for a bit.
Heading to the Arctic.
What's going on here?
Is this rappelling?
Xiao Hu's expression could totally be made into a meme.
This is just like a drama.
Watching this almost makes me want to cry.
Come on, Lao Wo, hold his hand.
And they're even interlocking fingers.
Uh-oh, that's the sour smell of love.
Maybe I didn't notice that about him.
The way he reached out and then pulled his hand back.
There's still a lot.
Of guilt.
You're outside the door.
The way you suddenly jumped on.
That kind of thing suddenly feels so cute to me.
Really?
You still find it easier to make friends with people from Qingdao.
It's that people from Qingdao like me more.
We really do all like you.
That caught you off guard, didn't it?
The people we like all have the same style.
So, what do you think?
Did you have fun today?
Yes, I had fun.
I had fun.
Like this.
Of these three, which one do you like best?
Of course, I'm not playing anymore.
Using public power for personal revenge.